bulbhead.com 2017-06-13

# Privacy Policy | BulbHead

### 1\.  Introduction

Thank you for visiting BulbHead.com.  This privacy policy applies to the Bulbhead.com website only. Please read this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions carefully, as by using the Service you agree to be bound by both documents. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us via email at [policies@bulbhead.com](mailto:policies@bulbhead.com).

### 2\.  Definitions

In this Privacy Policy, we use the following definitions:

  * “BulbHead” or “we” or “us” refers to our company, known as “BulbHead.com”; our Site; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context in whichthe word is used;
  * “Service” refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including our Site itself;
  * “Site” refers to our website, [www.bulbhead.com](http://www.bulbhead.com/);
  * “User” refers to anyone who uses our Service, including general visitors to our Site;
  * “You” refers to you, the User. 

### 3\.  Information Collected 

Identifying Information

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service and/or engage in transactions via our Site that can be used to identify you, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, PayPal address (if different from e-mail address), mailing address, credit card information, and telephone number.

If you post comments, images or other content on our Site, anything that you post becomes public to all Site users – whether it is personally identifying of you or not -- and we disclaim any responsibility for any subsequent use by anyone else of any such information that you post publicly. We do retain the right to remove any comment, image or other content that you post.

Our Site also collects certain other information, such as your IP address, information collected by “cookies,” and purchase history that does not itself identify you but could do so if it were to be combined with sufficient other information.

We may allow third-party services to collect information about how our Users use Bulbhead.com or use other websites across the Internet. For more information about these services, see Section 6.

Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your referring URL, pages viewed, length of visit, browser, operating system, and Internet Service Provider.  Without additional information, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you. 

### 4\.  Use of Your Information

The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is used and/or disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Our primary use of personal information is to provide you with the Services that you request.

We may also use your personal information to:

  * Enhance or improve User experience, our Site, or our Service.
  * Verify registration status.
  * Process transactions.
  * Provide products or information that you purchase or request.
  * Send e-mails about your transactions or our Site, or to respond to inquiries.
  * Send e-mails, including our e-mail newsletter, and updates about BulbHead and other products available via the Site.
  * Send e-mails and updates about BulbHead, including our e-mail newsletter.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service. 
  * Respond when required by subpoena, warrant or other legal process.

Third, where allowed by law, we may also contact you regarding Services and products we believe you would find of interest. 

Finally, we may generate aggregated tracking information for traffic accounting and content analysis. Such aggregated statistical information is not directly linked to any personal information and cannot be used to identify you or any individual user of our Web Sites. We may share this aggregated information with other companies for the purpose of documenting site use and related data analytics.

We retain personal information of our registered users for as long as they remain registered, and for a reasonable time thereafter.

### 5\.  Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information

You may review and edit personal information you have provided to us by logging into your registered account on the Site and editing your account information.  Some information may not be edited or removed unless you delete your account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache.  We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in your other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability for such.  In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.

SEE SECTION 15 BELOW FOR IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS ON THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION 5.

### 6\.  Cookies

"Cookies" are small data files stored on your computer&#39;s hard drive. Like most websites, we use cookies provide you with a personalized and enhanced online experience by actions such as remembering your preferences, tracking advertisements, and remembering your shopping cart items.  For these reasons, you need to enable cookies in your browser to have full use of our Site. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of the Site. 

Like many other websites, we use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other technologies on our Site to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions. In particular, we may use third-party advertising services on our Site, such as Google AdSense, for purposes such as:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense;
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting; and
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

To learn more about the DoubleClick cookie, including how to uninstall it, please visit <https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090?hl=en>. 

Our website may use services that track a user’s browsing not only within Bulbhead.com but also across other websites. Those services do not collect the Identifying Information as defined above, although they may make use of persistent identifiers that could allow particular content or advertising to be presented to a particular User.

Some browsers send so-called “Do Not Track” signals to websites such as ours. Our Site currently does not honor such indications due to a lack of industry consensus as to how such signals should be handled.

### 7\.  Third Party Websites

BulbHead may post links to third-party websites on its Site.  We have no control over these third-party websites, and those third-party websites have their own privacy policies that may differ from ours. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third-party links.

SEE SECTION 15 BELOW FOR IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS ON THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION 7.

### 8\.  Third Party Access to Your Information

We use other companies to provide support to our Site and our Services, and we may need to share information about you with these companies, or they may collect it directly, so that they can provide their services to us and ultimately to you. For example, our web hosting service stores the personal information that you provide us, and we use a logistics company to handle order processing and shipments. Our contracts with those companies prohibit those companies from making use of your personal information for any purpose other than to assist our Site and Service. In some cases, those companies may allow subcontractors to access personal information of BulbHead.com users for the purpose of providing their services to us. 

A third-party payment processor, such as PayPal, handles payments. By making a purchase on the Site, you authorize us to collect, share, and otherwise use your information in conjunction with our payment processor. Our payment processor stores all credit-card information; BulbHead itself does not retain credit card numbers.

We do not rent or sell the personal information of our Users with non-affiliated third parties for their own use. We may share such personal information with our parent company, Telebrands, and other companies similarly under Telebrands’ ownership or control.

SEE SECTION 15 BELOW FOR IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS ON THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION 8.

### 9\.  Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes

At times BulbHead may be required by law to release personal information in response to a legal request from a government agency or a private litigant. If we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may try to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either, and in certain cases we may be prohibited from notifying you.  We also reserve the right to report you, and release personal information about you to, law enforcement or other appropriate third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities. 

SEE SECTION 15 BELOW FOR IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS ON THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION 9.

### 10\.  Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications

By providing us with your contact information, you authorize us to contact you regarding your use of the Site and Services, including any transactions in which you engage. You may unsubscribe from certain commercial email communications by notifying BulbHead that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information via opt-out or change of preferences links in our email communications.

SEE SECTION 15 BELOW FOR IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS ON THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION 10.

### 11\. Our Policies Regarding Children

We do not knowingly collect or maintain information from those under the age of 13.  If you are under 18 years of age, you may not become a registered user of our Site or otherwise access the Site. We do not sell products for purchase by children. 

### 12\. Security Measures

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates, vulnerability scanning, and PCI DSS-compliant hosting. We review and update our security measures as appropriate. However, no transmission of data over the Internet is completely secure, and we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

### 13\. Your California Privacy Rights

California residents have certain rights under state law. Under _California  Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579_, if you are a California resident you may request certain information about the types of personally identifiable information that we have shown with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please contact us at [policies@bulbhead.com](mailto:policies@bulbhead.com). 

### 14\.  International Transfer

We may transfer personal information to a call center outside of the United States. In addition, we may store personal information about you on computers located outside of your state, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may differ from those in your jurisdiction.  

In all such cases, our arrangements with any non-U.S. service providers prohibit them from using personal data for any purpose other than to provide support to our Site and Services.

### 15\.  Exclusions and Limitations; Consumer Protection Notice

If you are a consumer, the provisions in this Privacy Policy are intended to be only as broad and inclusive as is permitted by the laws of your State of residence. If you are a New Jersey consumer, the terms of Sections 5, 7, 8, 9, and 10 do not limit or waive your rights as a consumer under New Jersey law and the provisions in this Privacy Policy are intended to be only as broad and inclusive as is permitted by the laws of the State of New Jersey. In any event, BulbHead reserves all rights, defenses and permissible limitations under the law of your State of residence.

### 16\.  International Users

Our Site is designed and targeted for audiences and Users in the United States, and adheres to United States privacy laws. If you are using this Site while in another nation, please be advised that BulbHead transfers personal information to the United States and that U.S. law governs any personal information that you submit to us.

### 17\.  Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will update this page accordingly.  Your continued use of our Service shall constitute your acceptance of any such amendments.

 Effective Date: October 1, 2016
